(Sheldon:)That seems a fairly efficient arrangement.
(Beverley:)Yes, we think so.
We've both done papers on it.
Mine from a neuroscientific point of view
and his from an anthropological.
(Beverley:)Mine, of course,
was the only one worth reading.
(Leonard(entering on the phone):)Of course.
(Sheldon:)I would very much like
to read about your sex life.
(Beverley:)Well, it's all online or you can order it
from the Princeton University Press.
(Leonard:)Here's your tea, Mother.
(Leonard:)So, what are you guys talking about?
(Sheldon:)The frequency with which your parents
had intercourse.
(Leonard:)Swell.
(Leonard:)If you're lucky, maybe she'll show you
the PowerPoint presentation.
(Beverley:)I'm sorry, it's on my other laptop.
[GROANS]
(Leonard:)So, Mother...
(Leonard:)- ...what's new?
- You'll have to be more specific.
(Leonard:)All right. Uh, what's new with you?
(Beverley:)Oh, well, I've been having some fascinating
menopausal symptoms recently.
Maybe something less personal?